<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="team_numbers">

    <item>2180</item>
    <item>391</item>
    <item>9999999999</item>
        
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Questions_TELE">
        <item>Power-Up Cubes can be handled by Robot?</item>
        <item>Short Switch can have cubes placed in it by Robot?</item>
        <item>Tall Scale can have cubes placed in it by Robot?</item>
        <item>Cubes on the Floor can be manipulated by Robot?</item>
        <item>Cubes can be loaded onto the robot via the Players' Chutes?</item>
        <item>Number of Cubes loaded via the Players' Chutes:</item>
        <item>Maximum Cubes Robot is able to handle at once:</item>
        <item>Cubes Robot can place on Tall Scale during Teleop:</item>
        <item>Successful Attempts to place Cubes onto Scale during Teleop:</item>
        <item>Unsucessful Attempts to place Cubes onto Scale during Teleop:</item>
        <item>Cubes Robot can place on Small Switch during Teleop:</item>
        <item>Sucessful Attempts to place Cubes onto Switch during Teleop:</item>
        <item>Unsucessful Attempts to place Cubes onto Switch during Teleop:</item>
        <item>[ENDGAME] Robot is able to climb Tall Scale?</item>
        <item>[ENDGAME] Climbed the Tall Scale using a Bar?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Questions_AUTO">
        <item>Does the team have an autonomous period?</item>
        <item>Does autonomous cross the Base Line?</item>
        <item>Cubes Robot can place on Tall Scale:</item>
        <item>Sucessful Attempts to place Cubes onto Scale:</item>
        <item>Unsucessful Attempts to place Cubes onto Scale:</item>
        <item>Cubes Robot can place on Small Switch:</item>
        <item>Sucessful Attempts to place Cubes onto Switch:</item>
        <item>Unsucessful Attempts to place Cubes onto Switch:</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Questions_MISC">
        <item>Robot was disabled during match?</item>
        <item>Did the robot have ramps?</item>
        <item>Did the robot use ramps?</item>
        <item>Did the robot park correctly?</item>
        <item>Can this robot carry other robots?</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
